[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "But did it surprise you that in that moment, even at his young age, that he was showing such enterprising courage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "That's what's said happened and that's what's going around, that the kids made or were attempting to make a run or to escape.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What are your feelings towards the shooter himself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "My feelings towards the shooter is, it was a cowardly thing he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What is the most constructive, definitive thing that America's lawmakers can now do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "You know, there is no single, simple solution.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["state Supreme Court"], "LOCATION": ["Connecticut"]}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Are you really sensing, from your colleagues, that this is a tipping point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "I really am sensing that there is an openness and willingness on the part of a lot of people who never would have considered before to actually consider, for example, a ban on assault weapons which, as everybody knows, were designed for military use and right now even in the states that have them, like my state of Connecticut, and I know because I helped write the bill and then I personally defended it in court, in the trial, in the argument before state Supreme Court when it was challenged constitutionally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Have you noticed this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "There's been an outpouring all across America of people wanting to help and to give.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Are you optimistic that there will be one before we all tumble over this cliff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I am hopeful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Mr. Keller, you agree with Rick Perry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Yes, sir, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Keller", "Rick Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "And your idea is that all teachers would be armed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "ELLER: No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "That's correct, whether it be the weapons or the concealed carry class that I teach, either one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Where would these teachers who are armed put the guns when they are in school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I've thought about that a lot in the last couple of days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you sell AR-15 rifles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "-NONE-", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "When we can get them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "ELLER: I'm just -- I'm against any banning of any weapons that we are today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "I'm aware of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "That would be your solution?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "No, that's not the solution, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "You are aware that these weapons did unleash many, many, many bullets, are you, and killed many, many people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "My comment was that the person who is defending his place, whether it be a school or a theater, if they are trained properly, they can shoot one time and they take out the person who is spraying bullets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "This must have brought back particularly painful memories to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes, it certainly did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "But it wasn't political in anyway like the same way back in Britain, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "No, it wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain", "U.S.", "England"]}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What impact did the ban on handguns have in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, the level of gun crime in Britain is very low compared with the U.S. Gun crime has been falling in England every year for the last eight years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I just do not understand the logic of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dunblane"]}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Is there any advice that you can give them, any words of comfort from somebody who's, quite literally, lived through what they've gone through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I think one of the main strengths that those of us who lost children in Dunblane found was being brought together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I think when a thing like this happens, obviously all questions are on the table and deserve an answer, if you can get one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "\"The Sopranos,\" much missed show, one of my favorites on television, when it came to an end, what were your honest feelings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I was very happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elvis Costello"]}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "VBP", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Did you hope to have one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Here's all I remember coherently, was that there's this Elvis Costello song \"Radio, Radio,\" the lyrics of which are \"I want to bite the hand that feeds me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I was lucky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Why now, quite late in your career, to plunge into the big screen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I tried very hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Why did you want him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I didn't -- I wasn't thinking about Jim originally for this, for the role of the father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "''", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "They're suggesting it's kind of autobiographical for you, that when you were young, you wanted to be a rock star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I wanted to be a rock 'n' roll musician.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Didn't see yourself on stage, long hair, big guitar, strutting your stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Are you ever happy with your work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I -- I am happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "You were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Is that a compliment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]